那就是7票对Doyle的5票 那就是"冗长辩论"派的绝杀啊
That's seven to Doyle's five. I mean, this is a filibuster slam dunk.
- Chung在直播电视节目上 - 什麽?!
- Chung is on TV live. - What?!
- 快打开 快打开 - 遥控器呢?
- Get it on. Get it on. - Where's the remote?
在碗里 遥控器在碗里
It's in the bowl. The remote's in the bowl.
Sue 按按乐在哪里?
Sue, where's the clicker?
- 按按乐在哪里? - 同志们 在书柜里呢
- Where's the clicker? - Guys, it's in the credenza.
拿来 快 快 快
Get it. Quick, quick, quick.
- 什麽频道? 频道? - 直播的都行
- What channel? Channel? - Any live TV.
Mike...不 Mike 别碰那个遥控器 搞不好你要发射原子弹的
Mike... no, Mike. Don't touch that remote. You're gonna launch a nuke or something.
- Sue? - 这是关于今天早些时候评论所做的简单回应
- Sue? - A few brief words about the comments that were made earlier today.
尽管在互联网上有一些阴暗的流言
Despite what is said in some dark corners of the Internet,
但在我出生的时候
when I was born, both my parents
我的父母都是完全的归化美国公民
were fully naturalized American citizens.